A Guide to the Blake W. Corson, Jr., Papers, 1861-1984 (Bulk, 1934-1979)
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Series IV: Professional Projects, 1937-1984, n.d.
  - Subseries A: Research Tunnels (Folder 10, Folder 12, Folder 13, Folder 14, Folder 15, Folder 16, Folder 17)
    - Sub-subseries i: AERL Deicing (Folder 11)
      - AERL Ice Tunnel-- Simulated Propeller Icing (Department Meeting; Summary/Figures), 1944 (Box 1, Folder 141)
    - Sub-subseries ii: Propeller Research Tunnel
      - P.R.T. Torque Dynamometer (Drawings), n.d. (Box 2, Folder 1)
      - P.R.T. Propeller Blade Deflection--Report, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 2)
      - P.R.T. Propeller--Analysis/Graphs/Notes, 1937, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 3)
      - P.R.T. Propeller: Aerodynamic and Stress Analysis-- Graphs/Notes, 1937-1938 (Box 2, Folder 4)
      - P.R.T. Full Scale Tunnel: Wooden Propeller--Calculation/Graphs/ Notes, 1938, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 5)
      - P.R.T. Wood Propoeller--Calculations/Graphs/Notes, 1938, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 6)
      - 19 Foot P.R.T. Wooden Propeller Hub Specifications-- Notes/Report, 1937, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Sub-subseries iii: Two Dimensional Pressure Tunnel
      - Two Dimensional Pressure Tunnel Propeller VI (F-6159; A-Twisted) -- Calculations/Notes/Tables, 1938, 1939, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 8)
      - Two Dimension Pressure Tunnel Specifications-- Notes/Report (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Sub-subseries iv: High Speed Tunnel (Folder 14)
      Materials from this sub-subseries are in Box 2 (folders listed below) and in oversize Folder 14.
      - High Speed Wind Tunnel Propeller Design Charts-- Notes/Tables, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 10)
      - High Speed Tunnel Boundary Layer-- Calculations/Data/Graphs, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 11)
      - High Speed Tunnel--Combined Correlation and Friction/ Horsepower Tests--Calculations/Graphs/Tables, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 12)
      - High Speed Tunnel Propellers--Obsolete Design (Calculations/Graphs/Notes), 1939, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 13)
      - High Speed Tunnel-- Rear Propeller (Graphs/Tables), 1940, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 14)
      - High Speed Tunnel: Front Propeller-- Calculations/Graphs/Notes, 1940-1942, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 15)
      - High Speed Tunnel Counter Balance for Rear Propeller--Calculations/Design/ Notes, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 16)
      - High Speed Wind Tunnel: Fan Calibrations, 1954-1956, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Sub-subseries v: Moffett Field
      - Moffett Field: Scale Tunnel Propeller and Variable Pitch--Figures/Notes, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 18)
      - Moffett Field Rear Propeller-- Calculations/Graphs/Notes, 1939, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 19)
      - Moffett Field Front Propeller Specifications-- Calculations/Notes, 1939, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 20)
      - Moffett Field Front Propeller Hub--Calculations/Graphs/Notes, 1939, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 21)
      - Moffett Field Wind Tunnel Propeller--Calculations/Graphs/Notes, 1939, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 22)
      - Moffett Field Tunnel Propellers-- Calculations/Figures/Graphs/Photographs/Notes, 1942-1944 (Box 2, Folder 23)
        Becker, John Vernon, 1913- -- Correspondence; Johnson, E. -- Correspondence; Bierman, David -- Correspondence
    - Sub-subseries vi: 20 Foot Spin Tunnel
      - 20 Foot Spin Tunnel Propeller Hub Design-- Calculations/Notes, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - 20 Foot Spin Tunnel Obsolete Designs-- Calculations/Graphs/Tables, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - 20 Foot Spin Tunnel Propeller Acceleration Stress Analysis, 1939, n.d.-1940 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - 20 Foot Spin Tunnel: 5 Blade Propeller Design--Calculations/Notes, 1939, 1940, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - 20 Foot Spin Tunnel Propeller Hub--Calculations/Drawings/Notes, 1940, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 28)
      - 20 Foot Spin Tunnel: 3 Blade Propeller-- Calculations/Notes/Tables, 1940, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Sub-subseries vii: Stability Tunnel (Folder 9)
      Materials from this sub-subseries are in Box 2 (folders listed below) and in oversize Folder 9.
      - 6ft by 6ft Stability Tunnel Propeller--Calculations/Notes, 1940, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 30)
      - Stability Tunnel: Origional Motor Housing, Cooling, and Countervanes--Calculations/Notes, 1940, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 31)
      - Stability Tunnel Propeller Hub--Notes/Tables, 1940, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 32)
      - Stability Tunnel Countervanes--Notes/Graphs (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - Sub-subseries viii: Carderock Wind Tunnel (Folder 12)
      Materials from this sub-subseries are in Box 2 (folders listed below) and in oversize Folder 12.
      - Carderock Wind Tunnel--Figures/Graphs, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 34)
      - Carderock Wind Tunnel Design--Figures/Notes, 1943, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - Flutter Tunnel--Figures/Report, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - Gust Tunnel: Propellers-- Drawings/Notes, 1943, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Subseries B: Propellers and Propeller Research (Folder 8)
    Materials from this sub-subseries are in Box 2 (folders listed below) and in oversize folders (listed below), as well as in oversize Folder 8.
    - Sub-Subseries i: Propeller Theory
      - Propeller Theory-- Bibliography Outline, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 38)
      - "A Review of Propeller Theory"-- Draft, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 39)
      - "A Review of Propeller Theory" (By Blake W. Corson), n.d. (Box 2, Folder 40)
      - Propeller Theory Airfoil Characteristics--Figures, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 41)
      - Propeller Theory Airfoil Characteristics--Negative Figures, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 42)
      - Analysis of Propeller Data: Induced Angle--Calculations/Notes, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 43)
      - Indication of Velocity Distribution by a Catenary, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 44)
      - NACA Propellers--Figures, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Air Psychrometric Chart for Various Pressures, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Hooded Propellers--Origional Figures 2-56 (Mastrocola), n.d. (Folder 6, Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Westphal Compressor--Graphs/Notes, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Free Vortex--Calculations/Notes, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - XSC: Temperature Dispersion Engine Tests--Tables, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Engine Cooling Correlation--Report, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - 7'by 10' Wind Tunnel: Motor Cooling and Fairing--Calculations/Notes, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - 12 ft Free Flight Propeller--Data/Notes, 193, 1944, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Sub-subseries ii: XF4U-1
      - XF4U-1--Photographs, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 54)
      - XF4U-1--Reports, 1938, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 55)
      - Wind Tunnel Tests for Vought XF4U-1-- NACA Report, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 56)
      - XF4U-1 Extract: Model Tests of a Wing Duct System for Auxililary Air Supply--Report, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 57)
      - Vought XF4U-1 Cuff-- Data/Graphs, 1941, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Wind Tunnel Fan Design (TN-820)--Charts, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Wind Tunnel Fan Design--Figures/Graphs/Notes, 1940, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Martian B-26: Modified Cowling, Entrance Computations, Cuff Design, 1941, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Hooded Propellers-- Draft, 1941-1942, n.d. (Folder 6, Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Preliminary Hooded Propellers Program Tests--Report, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 63, Folder 6)
    - Propeller: P-62--Graphs/Notes, 1941, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - E.R.L. Cleveland Wind Tunnel --Propeller Check:Analysis; Cleveland, 1941 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Two Balde Propeller at High Forward Speed--Report, Ca. 1941, 1944 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Sub-subseries iii: Bell P-39 (Folder 4)
      - Bell Cuff Design: P-39--Graphs/Tables, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 67)
      - Bell: P-39 (H.S.T. Tests)-- Calculations/Drawings/Notes/Photographs, 1942, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Sub-subseries iv: XA-26
      - XA-26: Propellers and Drag Computations--Report, 1942, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 69)
      - XA-26: Directions--Calculations/Notes, 1942, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 70)
      - XA-26: Propeller and Drag Computations--Graphs/Tests, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 71)
      - XA-26: Propeller and Drag Computations--Notes (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Sub-subseries v: XSB2D-1 Propeller
      - Douglas XSB2D-1: Propeller Tests 210 and 211--Data/Graphs/Summary, 1942, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 73)
      - XSB2D-1: Fuel Flow Data-- Tables, 1942, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 74)
      - XSB2D-1: Tests and Calculations Relative to the State of Air in the Test Section-- Calculations/Data/Graphs, 1942, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 75)
      - XSB2D-1: Old Baffels--Calculations/Notes, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 76)
      - XSB2D-1: Old and New Baffels(Obsolete Curves)--Graphs/Notes (Box 2, Folder 77)
      - XSB2D-1: Engine Correlations and Preliminary Analysis--Graphs/Note (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Flight Information Tables, n.d. (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Sub-subseries vi: Goldstein and Blade Theory
      - Ideal Propeller Efficiency: Propeller Design Data-- Clark-Y/Goldstien, 1940-1942, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 1)
      - Goldstien Vortex Theory: Elemental Efficiency-- Figures/Graphs, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 2)
      - Goldstien Design and Aircraft Propeller Design--Calculations/Notes, 1942, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 3)
      - Blade Element Theory: Goldstien Vortex & Dual Rotation--Calculations/Graphs/Notes, 1942-1944, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 4)
        Quarles, L. R.
      - Goldstien Correction Factor for Vortex Blade Theory--Graphs, 1942-1943 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Glauert Propeller: Data Corrections due to Wind Tunnel Inference--Graphs/Notes, 1942, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Propeller Maximum Thickness: Typical Distribution--Figures, 1942 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Course Roll--Aircraft Propellers, 1942, 1945, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Sub-subseries vii: Pratt and Whitney R 2800 Engine
      - R 2800-27: Engine Friction Tests, 1943, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 9)
      - R2800 Pratt and Whitney Engine-- Friction, Horsepower, and Heat Balance Data, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 10)
        Bierman, David
      - R2800 Correlation-- Figures 16- 18, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 11)
      - R 2800 Heat Balance Charts-- Figures/Notes/Reports, 1944, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Curtis-Writght Corporation: Propeller Division Charts, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Bureau of Standards: Wind Tunnel Fan-- Drawings/Notes, 1943, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Propeller Wind Tests--Reports, 1943, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Negative Thrust Considerations-- Calculations/Figures, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Rotating Mercury Seal: Pressure Transfer Device--Notes, 1943, 1945, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Power Stability of Three Polar Variables--Calculations/Graphs/Notes, 1944, n.d.-1946 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - NACA--ESMDT Course--Propeller Notes, 1945, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Propeller Symbols--Figures/Index, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Turbine Driven Propeller--Notes, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Propeller Symbols--Index/Negatives/Tables, 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Sub-subseries viii: Pusher Propeller
      - Vibratory Stress--Calculations/Data/Graphs/Notes, 1945-46, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 23)
      - Pusher Propeller: Blade Three Vibratory Stress(200 mph)--Graphs/Notes/Tables, 1946, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Pusher Propeller: Blade Three Vibratory Stress (300mph)-- Graphs/Tables (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - Pusher Propeller: Blade Three Vibratory Stress--With Flutter, 1946, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Sub-subseries ix: Sweptback Propeller
      - " Calculation of Space Locus for Blade Section Centeroid of Swept Propeller"--Figures/Report, 1946, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 27)
      - Calculated Sweptback Propeller Efficiency--Conference Chart, 1946, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - Sweptback Propeller Structural Analysis-- Graphs/Notes, 1946, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Method of Reducing Propeller Stress and Vibration, 1946-1947 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Pressure Distribution on Rotating Propeller--Graphs/Notes, 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - University Conference On Aerodynamics--A Review of Propeller Theory, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Wind Tunnel Fan Design(Lift Coefficient and Alpha Corrections due to Solidity), 1948 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Sub-subseries x: Slotted Test Section
      - Slotted Test Section: Obsolete Computations--Calculations/Data, 1948, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 34)
      - Slotted Test Section--Choking Speed, Re-entrance Area Limitation, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 35)
      - Slotted Test Section: One Dimensional Analysis-- Calculations/Graphs, 19948, 1956, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 36)
      - Slotted Test Section: Viscous Flow at Slot Entrance--Calculations/Drawings/Graphs, 1949, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Ring Vortex--Calculations/Drawings, 1949, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - "Propeller Inflow Corrections at High Subsonic Mach Numbers"-- Calculations/Report, 1949, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Sub-subseries xi: Propeller Induced Camber
      - Induced Angle Propeller--Calculations/Drawings/Notes, 1949, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - Propeller Induced Camber Tests [(10/3049/03), (10/3066/03), (10/3090/03), (16/3090/03)]-- Data/Graphs, 1949-1950, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Propeller Induced Camber--Drafts/Notes/Reports, 1950, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Propeller Induced Camber-- Notes, 1950, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 43)
      - Propeller Induced Camber--Calculations/Notes, 1950, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Propeller Design for Constant Centrifugal Stress--Report, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Submarine Propulsive System--Figures/Report, 1950, 1959, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Langley 2000 Horse Power Propeller--Photographs, Ca. 1952 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Tripple Rotart Joint: Model String Support--Calculations/Drawings/Notes/Report, 1952-1953, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Sub-subseries xii: Ski Wing
      - Ski Wing--Drawings/Proposal, 1952, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 49)
      - Ski Wing Analysis-- Photographs/Proposal, 1953 (Box 3, Folder 50)
      - Ski Wing: Tests-- Graph/Photographs, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Propeller Blade Vibration Research, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Corotational Tangent Rotors--Calculations/Drawings/Notes, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Sub-subseries xiii: Jet Exit Research
      - Nacelle Aspect Ratio Coefficients: Drag--Calculations/Graphs/Notes (Box 3, Folder 54)
      - TFX Jet Exit Research-- Calculations/Drawings/Notes, 1955-1960, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 55)
      - Jet Exit Research--Analysis/Notes, 1957, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 56)
      - Jet Exit Research: Air Powered Nacelle (Tri Tunnel Model)-- Notes/Report, 1963, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 57)
      - Summary of Research on Jet Exit Installations--Report, 1966, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 58)
      - Jet Exit Research: Exhaust Nozzle VTOL Models, 1971, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 59)
      - Jet Over Wing Propulsion: Nacalle-- Drawings/Purchase Request, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - Sub-subseries ivx: Jet Noise Suppression
      - Jet Noise Suppression--Notes/Report, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 61)
      - Jet Noise Supression-- Calculations/Notes, 1956-1958, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 62)
      - Multiple Annular Jet Noise Suppressor, 1957-1959 (Box 3, Folder 63)
      - Jet Noise Suppression--Refrences, 1971, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 64)
    - Flow Entrainment: Circular Jet-- Calculations/Data/Figures/Notes, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 65)
    - Propeller Static: Ideal Effect Coefficient-- Graphs/Notes, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 66)
    - XP6M-1 Problems--Analysis, 1957, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 67)
    - Valveless Pulse Jet--Notes/Photographs, 1960, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 68)
    - Aerodynamics of Wind Tunnel Fan (TN 820)--Notes, 1961, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 69)
    - Supersonic Propeller Efficiency -- Data/Graphs, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 70)
    - Apollo Escape Craft-- Drawings/Notes, 1962, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 71)
    - TRECOM Hiller Data: Helicopter Blade Tip Mounted Turbojet--Comments/Notes, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 72)
    - Sub-subseries vx: Multiple Cell Toridal Vortex Tube (Folder 10)
      - Multiple Cell Toridal Vortex Tube--Negative Figures (1,2,4,7,8), 1964 (Box 3, Folder 73)
      - Multiple Cell Toridal Vortex Tube--Patent Transparencies, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 74)
      - Multiple Cell Toridal Vortex Tube--Patent Manuscript, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 75)
      - Multiple Cell Toridal Vortex Tube--Patent Figures (1-8), 1964 (Box 3, Folder 76)
      - Multiple Cell Toridal Vortex Tube--Patent Figure 1, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 77)
      - Multiple Cell Toridal Vortex Tube--Patent Figure 2, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 78)
      - Multiple Cell Toridal Vortex Tube--Patent Figure 4, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 79)
      - Multiple Cell Toridal Vortex Tube--Patent Figure 7, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 80)
      - Multiple Cell Toridal Vortex Tube--Patent Figure 8, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 81)
      - Multiple Cell Toridal Vortex Tube--Patent, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 82)
      - Patent Copy--Multiple Cell Toridal Vortex Tube, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 83)
      - Vortex Tube Model--Calculations/Notes/Tables (William R. Bobo), 1964, n.d.-1965 (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Surge Control Valve--Graphs/Notes/Report, 1965, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - XC-142A Propeller--Calculations/Graphs/Notes, 1965, n.d., 1966 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Subseries C: Nozzles and Nozzle Research (Folder 7)
    Materials from this subseries are in Box 4 (folders listed below) and in oversize Folder 7.
    - Nozzle Installation and Pressure Ratio--Figures(1, 5-8), n.d. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Mechanical Sink: Supersonic Nozzle-- Notes/Proposal, 1947-1961 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Dual Flow Nozzle--Report (copies), 1948 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Dual Passage Nozzle-- Figures/Report, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Sub-subseries i: Perforated Difusser Nozzle
      - Perforated Diffuser Nozzle-- Photographs, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 5)
      - Perforated Difusser Nozzle-- Notes/Report, 1953, 1957, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Sub-subseries ii: Bifurcated Rotary Joint
      - Biofurcated Rotary Joint: "Sting"--Analysis/Notes, 1952, 1954, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 7)
      - Bifurcated Rotary Joint Support-- Wind Tunnel Models, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Bifurcated Rotary Joint Support for Wind Tunnel Models-- Patent Application, 1954-1958 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Sub-subseries iii:Cascade Plug Nozzle (Folder 5)
      Materials from this sub-subseries are in Box 4 (folders listed below) and in oversize Folder 5.
      - Figures(1-4, 6-7)--Ratio of Average Incompressible Turbulent skin Friction to Karman Schoenherr's Formula, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Nozzle Loss and Skin Friction-- Calculations/Data/Draft/Graph, 1958, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Casacde Plug Nozzle--Calculations/Drawings, 1966, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Cascade Plug Nozzle: Mixed Flow Nozzle Turbofan Propulsion Simulation with an Air Driven Model Engine-- Graph/Notes/Report, 1969-1970, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Cascade Plug Nozzle: Test 266 (Corrected and Obsolete)-- Data/Notes, 1969-1972, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Cascade Plug Nozzle--Report Outline, 1971, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Cascade Plug Nozzle--Photographs, 1971, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Cascade Plug Nozzle-- Report Draft, 1971, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Cascade Plug Nozzle Model II--Graphs/Notes/Report/Tables, 1971, n.d.-1972 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - Cascade Plug Nozzle--Notes/Tables, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Cascade Plug Nozzle--Disclosure of Invention (NASA Case Number LAR 10951-1), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Cascade Plug Nozzle--Patent Copy, 1971-1977 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Cascade Plug Nozzle: Model III--Calculations/Data, 1972, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - Cascade Plug Nozzle:Model IV-- Calculations/Graphs/Notes, 1972, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - Cascade Plug Nozzle--Manuscript, 1972, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - Cascade Plug Nozzle: Model II Sketches, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - Cascade Plug Nozzle--Noise Measurements( E.p. McDavid)--Notes/Report, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - Cascade Plug Nozzle--Application For Patent, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 27)
      - Cascade Plug Nozzle: Signed Copy-- Patent (Box 4, Folder 28)
      - Cascade Plug Nozzle--Patent Plaque, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 29)
      - Cascade Plug Nozzle--Patent, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Sub-subseries iv: Annular Nozzle Concave Central Base
      - Annular Nozzle: Concave Central Base--Notes/Report, 1959, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 31)
      - Annular Nozzle: Concave Central Base-- Patent Notes, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 32)
      - Annular Nozzle: Concave Central Base-- Patent Manuscript, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 33)
      - Annular Nozzle: Concave Plug Base Thrust-- Calculations/Graphs/Tables, 1959, n.d., 1961 (Box 4, Folder 34)
      - Annular Nozzle: Concave Central Base-- Patent Data, 1959-1961 (Box 4, Folder 35)
      - Static Thrust on an Annular Jet Exit with a Concave Central Base--Notes/Report Draft, 1960, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 36)
      - Static Thrust of an Annular Jet Exit with a Concave Central Base-- Notes/Report, 1960, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 37)
      - Static Thrust of an Annular Jet Exit with a Concave Central Base--Report Copy (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Sub-subseries vi:Convergent Divergent Nozzle Ejector Performance and Charcteristics
      - Ejectors-- Calculations/Drawings/Notes, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 39)
      - Controlable Convergent Divergent Nozzle--Notes, 1954-1956, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 40)
      - Relationship of Flight Factors with Regards to Primary and Secondary Airflows or Ejectors--Calculations/Graphs/Notes, 1965, n.d.-66 (Box 4, Folder 41)
      - Ejector Performance with Secondary Ram Drag-- Calculations/Graphs/Notes, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 42)
      - Extension of Ejector Charts--Calculations/Graphs/Notes, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Sub-subseries v: Annular Nozzle with Semi-Toridal Base
      - Annular Nozzle with Semi-Toridal Concave Base--Calculations/ Drawings/Notes, 1961-1963, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 44)
      - Transonic Thrust Characteristics of an Annular Nozzle with Semi-Toridal Concave Base--Notes/Draft, 1962-1963, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 45)
      - Transonic Thrust and Drag Characteristics of an Annular Nozzle with Semi-Toridal Concave Base (Obsolete)--Draft, 1962-1963, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 46)
      - Transonic Thrust and Drag Characteristics of an Annular Nozzle with Semi-Toridal Concave Base--Figures, 1962-1963, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 47)
      - Transonic Thrust and Drag Characteristics of an Annular Nozzle with Semi-Toridal Concave Base--Notes/Report, 1962-1963, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 48)
      - Transonic Thrust and Drag Characteristics of an Annular Nozzle with Semi-Toridal Concave Base--Conversions(Static to Dynamic), 1962-1963, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Sub-subseries vi: Exhaust Nozzle and Jet Nozzle Performance
      - Exhaust Nozzle and Jet Effects Research-- Figures/Photographs, 1969, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 50)
      - Jet Nozzle-- Calculations/Notes, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 51)
      - Jet Nozzle Performance and Comparison--Notes/Calculations, 1969, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 52)
      - Nozzle Thrust Coefficient-- Graphs, 1967, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Sliding Block Nozzle--Calculations/Notes, 1968, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Airframe Afterbody Configuration Thrust and Drag-- Analysis/Drawings/Notes, 1968, n.d.-1969 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Thrust Modulator Effectiveness in Reverse Thrust Mode--Calculations/Notes/Report, 1969, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Comments on Analysis of Thrust and Drag Measurements on Airframe and Afterbody Nozzle Configurations, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Mixed Flow Nozzle Turbofan Propulsion Simulation with an Air Driven Model Engine--Calculations/Data/ Notes, 1969-1970, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Mixed Flow Nozzle Turbofan Propulsion Simulation with an Air Driven Model Engine-- Draft, 1970-1971, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Miscellaneous Nozzle Notes, 1967-1970, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - Subseries D: Research Projects
    - Variable Information: Sucession of Coordinates, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Study on Particle Behavior--Calculations/Drawings/Notes, 1937, n.d.-1938 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Sub-subseries i: Compressibility Research
      - Energy Relations and Compressible Flow--Notes/Report Draft, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 3)